<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>~/seanbowers.tech</title>
    <link>https://seanbowers.tech/</link>
    <description>Recent content on ~/seanbowers.tech</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© Sean Bowers</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2022 00:39:34 -0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://seanbowers.tech/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://seanbowers.tech/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2022 21:44:57 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seanbowers.tech/contact/</guid>
      <description>For event booking, job offers, or pledges of undying and eternal love and devotion, please email me at info@seanbowers.tech
the two places online where I can still be found LinkedIn FOSStodon (Mastodon instance for free and open source software devotees) </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What I Use</title>
      <link>https://seanbowers.tech/blog/what-i-use/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2022 00:39:34 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seanbowers.tech/blog/what-i-use/</guid>
      <description>Software of Choice Arch Linux This is the first in a series in which I want to highlight the software that I use on a regular basis. I have found some of my favorite software while reading other people&amp;rsquo;s similar blogs or articles. So I figured I would count myself among the many and return the favor.
While I believe Linux to be the only rational operating system of choice (This is a joke&amp;hellip;ish), I do find people&amp;rsquo;s choice of Linux distro to be of interest.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Links</title>
      <link>https://seanbowers.tech/links/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Nov 2022 23:15:46 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seanbowers.tech/links/</guid>
      <description>Links Here I am including links to some of my writing, interviews, videos, as well as IT certs and other blogs, Youtube channels, and other content I find interesting. I miss the days when people would include links to other peoples content. Hoping to bring back some of that community spirit from the internet of yesteryear. I must state that links to other people&amp;rsquo;s content does not act as a wholesale endorsement, and that their views or actions may or may not coincide with that of my own.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Web of Old</title>
      <link>https://seanbowers.tech/blog/web-of-old/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Nov 2022 22:27:36 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seanbowers.tech/blog/web-of-old/</guid>
      <description>I am one of those people that long for the internet of old. Simple, &amp;ldquo;bad design,&amp;rdquo; pure HTML, .gif playground. I love it!
According to modern standards, this would be considered bad design. But these graphics had imagination. Individuality. People made websites and graphics from scratch before we understood the technology. Now that we have the technology, our sites are bland, white washed, cookie cutter cutouts of every other boring site.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nextcloud Woes</title>
      <link>https://seanbowers.tech/blog/nextcloud-woes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Nov 2022 15:13:02 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seanbowers.tech/blog/nextcloud-woes/</guid>
      <description>So a number of years back, I realized that Google took up way too much of the cloud-based digital real estate in my life and the lives of everybody around me. Now, I feel that I have to stress that I am not anti-Google. While I loathe a number of business and tech practices of Google, as well as their parent company Alphabet, I must admit that they have made extraordinary progress in tech since their advent as a goofy-named search engine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://seanbowers.tech/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Nov 2022 11:57:42 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seanbowers.tech/about/</guid>
      <description>Sean Bowers spent his formative years in and out of juvenile corrections, on and off the streets. Bowers comes from a lineage of violence and addiction, that lead to over a decade of homelessness, gang violence, alcoholism &amp;amp; drug addiction, sex work, train hopping &amp;amp; hitch hiking, and eventual collapse into alcohol fueled isolation and depression. It wasn&amp;rsquo;t till his mid 20s that he was able to get sober and get off the street.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Borders and Boundaries</title>
      <link>https://seanbowers.tech/blog/borders-and-boundaries/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Nov 2022 02:08:15 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seanbowers.tech/blog/borders-and-boundaries/</guid>
      <description>Throughout my life, there have been a great number books and albums that have come at just the right time, that the only way to properly describe them is to say they &amp;ldquo;saved my life.&amp;rdquo; More often than not this is merely hyperbole. But in the case of the album Borders &amp;amp; Boundaries by Less Than Jake, it definitely carried me through the end of my drinking.
This is even more ironic as I don&amp;rsquo;t necessarily like Less Than Jake.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
